[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":51385,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":63980,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure tha t when w e combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":7778,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":71764,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":9315,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":81083,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":2249,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":83337,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":6473,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":89812,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1648,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":91464,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one t o it. If  the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1","0\n","0"],"rt":23668,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":115133,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1053,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":116189,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":5481,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":121671,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1263,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":122935,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":4058,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":126995,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +< sub>6</s ub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1081,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":128077,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":4141,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":132220,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1559,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":133781,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? < br /><br  /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":4080,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":137862,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1265,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":139129,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your  result. )","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":4143,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":143275,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1393,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":144671,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":3996,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":148668,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1844,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":150515,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":14231,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":164747,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1417,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":166167,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":11927,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":178100,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its ow n invers e under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":42534,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":220636,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":7068,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":227707,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2338,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":230047,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>?  <br /><b r /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6","5"],"rt":8473,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":238521,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1311,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":239834,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":8766,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":248602,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1173,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":249776,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":7462,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":257240,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the ident ity unde r +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":964,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":258206,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":11145,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":269352,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":5032,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":274385,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation  can simp ly be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":22313,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":296699,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<s ub>6</su b> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":97698,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":394399,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":20400,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":414801,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":5917,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":420720,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <b r /><br  /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":17686,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":438408,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":15111,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":453520,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? < br /><br  /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":39005,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":492527,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":3734,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":496263,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":5531,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":501797,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":925,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":502723,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with fe edback t o make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":19024,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":521748,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":5780,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":527531,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1177,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":528710,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":7069,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":535781,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":7856,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":543638,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":6985,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":550624,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":5079,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":555705,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":10419,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":566125,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":9741,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":575867,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Wha t is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"Four plus one is 5 and 5 is less than 9 so it is the answers. There's no need to subtract 9 because it is between 0 and 8.","explanation_history":["Foru","For","Four plus one is 5 and 5 is less than 9 so it j","Four plus one is 5 and 5 is less than 9 so it ","Four plus one is 5 and 5 is less than 9 so it is thean","Four plus one is 5 and 5 is less than 9 so it is thea","Four plus one is 5 and 5 is less than 9 so it is the answers. There's no need to add ","Four plus one is 5 and 5 is less than 9 so it is the answers. There's no need to add","Four plus one is 5 and 5 is less than 9 so it is the answers. There's no need to ad","Four plus one is 5 and 5 is less than 9 so it is the answers. There's no need to a","Four plus one is 5 and 5 is less than 9 so it is the answers. There's no need to su btract 9  bega","Four plus one is 5 and 5 is less than 9 so it is the answers. There's no need to subtract 9 begc","Four plus one is 5 and 5 is less than 9 so it is the answers. There's no need to subtract 9 beg","Four plus one is 5 and 5 is less than 9 so it is the answers. There's no need to subtract 9 because it is between 1","Four plus one is 5 and 5 is less than 9 so it is the answers. There's no need to subtract 9 because it is between 0 and 8."],"response_history":["5"],"rt":47330,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":623200,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"Eight plus four is twelve. Twelves is greater than nine so you subtract nine from twelve to get 3.","explanation_history":["Eight plus four is twelve. Te","Eight plus four is twelve. T welves i s greater than nine so you subtract nine form ","Eight plus four is twelve. Twelves is greater than nine so you subtract nine form","Eight plus four is twelve. Twelves is greater than nine so you subtract nine for","Eight plus four is twelve. Twelves is greater than nine so you subtract nine fo","Eight plus four is twelve. Twelves is greater than nine so you subtract nine from twelves","Eight plus four is twelve. Twelves is greater than nine so you subtract nine from twelve to get 3."],"response_history":["12","3"],"rt":43254,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":666456,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":true,"explanation":"I think the identity is 0 because it will always be less than nine.","explanation_history":["I thinkt he i","I thinkt he  ","I thi nkt he","I thinkt h","I thinkt ","I thinkt","I think the identity is 0 ebcau","I think the identity is 0 ebca","I think the identity is 0 ebc","I think the identity is 0 eb","I think the identity is 0 e","I think the identity is 0 becuase ","I think the identity is 0 becuase","I think the identity is 0 becuas","I think the identity is 0 becua","I think the identity is 0 becu","I think the identity is 0 because it will always been","I think the identity is 0 because it will always bee","I think the identity is 0 because it will always be less than nine."],"response_history":["Yhe","Yh","Y","0"],"rt":62729,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":729188,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":65784,"trial_type":"question ","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":794973,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["7"],"rt":14159,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":809134,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["9"],"rt":7163,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":816298,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":true,"explanation":"You add six to three to get nine and nine minus nine equals zero which is the identity.","explanation_history":["YOu ad","YOu a","YOu ","YOu","YO","You add 6 ","You add 6","You add six to three to get 9","You add six to three to get nine and nine mine","You add six to three to get nine and nine minus nine equals zero whcih ","You add six to three to get nine and nine minus nine equals zero whcih","You add six to three to get nine and nine minus nine equals zero whci","You add six to three to get nine and nine minus nine equals zero whc","You add six to three to get nine and nine minus nine equals zero which is the identity."],"response_history":["6"],"rt":55918,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":872217,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Ye s","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"You can got create all numbers between 0 and 8 using the +9 system and the number 2.","explanation_history":["You can't make any number greater than six using 2 so it can't genearat","You can't make any number greater than six using 2 so it can't geneara","You can't make any number greater than six using 2 so it can't genear","You can't make any number greater than six using 2 so it can't genea","You can't make any number greater than six using 2 so it can't generate all numbers in the system.","yes","ye","y","YOuc an ","YOuc an","You can mak","You can ma","You can m","You can got asu","You can got as","You can got a","You can got creat all","You can got creat al","You can got creat a","You can got creat ","You can got create all numbers w","You can got create all numbers between 1","You can got create all numbers between 0 abnd","You can got create all numbers between 0 abn","You can got create all numbers between 0 ab","You can  got crea te all numbers between 0 and 8 using the =","You can got create all numbers between 0 and 8 using the =","You can got create all numbers between 0 and 8 using the +9 system and the number 2."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":142632,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1014852,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"Yes, you can create all numbers between one and eight using 3 in the +9 system.","explanation_history":["Yes, c","Yes, you can create all numbers between a","Yes, you can create all numbers between one and eight using 3 and t","Yes, you can create all numbers between one and eight using 3 and ","Yes, you can create all numbers between one and eight using 3 and","Yes, you can create all numbers between one an d eight  using 3 an","Yes, you can create all numbers between one and eight using 3 a","Yes, you can create all numbers between one and eight using 3 in the =","Yes, you can create all numbers between one and eight using 3 in the =","Yes, you can create all numbers between one and eight using 3 in the +9 system."],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":89523,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1104377,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"Yes, you can create all numbers between 0 and 8 using the plus 9 system and the number 5.","explanation_history":["U","Yeas,","Yeas","Yea","Yes, you can creat al","Yes, you can creat a","Yes, you can creat ","Yes, you can creat","Yes, you can creae all","Yes, you can creae al","Yes, you can crea e a","Ye s, you can creae ","Yes, you can creae","Yes, you can create all numbers wb","Yes, you can create all numbers w","Yes, you can create all numbers between 0 and 8 using the plus 9 yste","Yes, you can create all numbers between 0 and 8 using the plus 9 yst","Yes, you can create all numbers between 0 and 8 using the plus 9 ys","Yes, you can create all numbers between 0 and 8 using the plus 9 y","Yes, you can create all numbers between 0 and 8 using the plus 9 system and the number 5\n.","Yes, you can create all numbers between 0 and 8 using the plus 9 system and the number 5\n","Yes, you can create all numbers between 0 and 8 using the plus 9 system and the number 5."],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":128886,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1233265,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"Yes, you can create all numbers between 1 and eight using 6 and the plus 9 system.","explanation_history":["Yes, you can create all numbertw","Yes, you can create all numbert","Yes, you can create all numbers between 1 and eight using 6 abd tge","Yes, you can create all numbers between 1 and eight using 6 abd tg","Yes, you can create all numbers between 1 and eight using 6 abd t","Yes, you can create all numbers between 1 and eight using 6 abd ","Yes, you can create all numbers between 1 and eight using 6 abd","Yes, you can create all numbers between 1 and eight using 6 ab","Yes, you can create all numbers between 1 and eight using 6 and the plus 9 ystem","Yes, you can create all numbers between 1 and eight using 6 and the plus 9 yste","Yes, you can create all numbers between 1 and eight using 6 and the plus 9 yst","Yes, you can create all numbers between 1 and eight using 6 and the plus 9 ys","Yes, you can crea te all n umbers between 1 and eight using 6 and the plus 9 y","Yes, you can create all numbers between 1 and eight using 6 and the plus 9 sty","Yes, you can create all numbers between 1 and eight using 6 and the plus 9 st","Yes, you can create all numbers between 1 and eight using 6 and the plus 9 system."],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":56265,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1289532,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":14897,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1304431,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 u nder +<s ub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1+n= 1(+n)I or I=1(+n)1+n when I=the inverse of 1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["I = n","I = ","I =","I ","I","n = n (+n)","1+n= n","1+n= ","1+n= 1(","1+n= 1 (+n)I or I=1(+n) 1+n","1+n= 1 (+n)I or I=1(+n) ]1+n","1+n=1(+n)IorI=1(+n)1+n","1+n=1(+n)IorI=1(+n)1+n","1+n=1(+n)IorI=1(+n)1+nwhenI=theinv","1+n=1(+n)IorI=1(+n)1+nwhenI=thein","1+n=1(+n)IorI=1(+n)1+nwhenI=thei","1+n=1(+n)IorI=1(+n)1+nwhenI=the","1+n=1(+n)IorI=1(+n)1+nwhenI=th","1+n=1(+n)IorI=1(+n)1+nwhenI=theinverseof1"],"rt":166815,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1471251,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"x+n=x(+n)I or I=x(+n)x+n","explain":true,"explanation":"The inverse of x will be x plus n when n is whatever number the system is based on.","explanation_history":["The inverst","The inverse of x will be an e","The inverse of x will be an ","The inverse of x will be an","The inverse of x will be a","The inverse of x will be x ","The inverse of x will be x plus n where ","The inverse of x will be x plus n where","The inverse of x will be x plus n wher","The inverse of x will be x plus n whe","The inverse of x will be x plus n wh","The inverse of x will be x plus n w","The inverse of x will be x plus n when n is whatever n","The inverse of x will be x plus n when n is whatever number the yste","The inverse of x will be x plus n when n is whatever number the yst","The inverse of x will be x plus n when n is whatever number the ys","The inverse of x will be x plus n when n is whatever number the y","The inverse of x will be x plus n when n is whatever num ber the  sytem is ","The inverse of x will be x plus n when n is whatever number the sytem is","The inverse of x will be x plus n when n is whatever number the sytem i","The inverse of x will be x plus n when n is whatever number the sytem ","The inverse of x will be x plus n when n is whatever number the sytem","The inverse of x will be x plus n when n is whatever number the syte","The inverse of x will be x plus n when n is whatever number the syts","The inverse of x will be x plus n when n is whatever number the syt","The inverse of x will be x plus n when n is whatever number the system is bad","The inverse of x will be x plus n when n is whatever number the system is based on."],"response_history":["x+n=x(+n) or ","x+n=x(+n) or","x+n=x(+n) o","x+n=x(+n) ","x+n=x(+n)I or I = (x","x+n=x(+n)I or I = (","x+n=x(+n)I or I = ","x+n=x(+n)I or I =","x+n=x(+n)I or I ","x+n=x(+n)I or I=x ","x+n=x(+n)I or I=x(+n)x+n"],"rt":105556,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1576808,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I'm not sure but I believe it has something to do with the number n and how small the generator is.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["I'm not sure but i","I'm not sure but I believe it has something to do with the number n and how small the genear","I'm not sure but I believe it has something to do with the number n and how small the genea","I'm not sure but I believe it has something to do with the number n and how small the generator is."],"rt":60254,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1637064,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number , it mus t be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":6629,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1643694,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":5934,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1649630,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","F alse"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":9596,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1659229,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"True","response":"False","explain":true,"explanation":"I'm not sure but I think for it to not be a generator it shouldn't be able to divide evenly into n because it would be a generator","explanation_history":["I'm not sure but I think for it to not be a genearate","I'm not sure but I think for it to not be a genearat","I'm not sure but I think for it to not be a geneara","I'm not sure but I think for it to not be a genear","I'm not sure but I think for it to not be a genea","I'm  not sure  but I think for it to not be a generator it should ","I'm not sure but I think for it to not be a generator it shouldn't be able to dev","I'm not sure but I think for it to not be a generator it shouldn't be able to de","I'm not sure but I think for it to not be a generator it shouldn't be able to divide evently into","I'm not sure but I think for it to not be a generator it shouldn't be able to divide evenly into n because ity ","I'm not sure but I think for it to not be a generator it shouldn't be able to divide evenly into n because ity","I'm not sure but I think for it to not be a generator it shouldn't be able to divide evenly into n because it would be a genr","I'm not sure but I think for it to not be a generator it shouldn't be able to divide evenly into n because it would be a generator"],"response_history":["False"],"rt":56000,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1715233,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an e lement x  is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":22364,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1737598,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Sometimes","response":"Sometimes","explain":true,"explanation":"Again, I believe it has something to do with the size of x in relation to n. If x is smaller than n it may not necessarily be a generator","explanation_history":["AGain","AGa i","AGa","AG","Again, I beleive i","Again, I beleive ","Again, I beleive","Again, I beleiv","Again, I belei","Again, I bele","Again, I believe ti ha","Again, I believe ti h","Again, I believe ti ","Again, I believe ti","Again, I believe t","Again, I believe it has someti","Again, I believe it has something to do with a ","Again, I believe it has something to do with a","Again, I believe it has something to do with the size of x in relativion ","Again, I believe it has something to do with the size of x in relativion","Again, I believe it has something to do with the size of x in relativio","Again, I believe it has something to do with the size of x in relativi","Again, I believe it has something to do with the size of x in relativ","Again, I believe it has something to do with the size of x in relatiio","Again, I believe it has something to do with the size of x in relatii","Again, I believe it has something to do with the size of x in relati","Again, I believe it has something to d o with t he size of x in relatt","Again, I believe it has something to do with the size of x in relation to n. if ","Again, I believe it has something to do with the size of x in relation to n. if","Again, I believe it has something to do with the size of x in relation to n. i","Again, I believe it has something to do with the size of x in relation to n. IF ","Again, I believe it has something to do with the size of x in relation to n. IF","Again, I believe it has something to do with the size of x in relation to n. If x is smaller than N ","Again, I believe it has something to do with the size of x in relation to n. If x is smaller than N","Again, I believe it has something to do with the size of x in relation to n. If x is smaller than n it may not necessarily be a generator"],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":118306,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1855906,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a genera tor unde r +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Never"],"rt":24953,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1880861,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1574,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1882437,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"26","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["26"],"rt":3085,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1885523,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":2768,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1888293,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"calculus","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["calcuslus","calcuslu","calcusl","calcus","calculus"],"rt":11380,"trial_type":"qu estion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1899675,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":5546,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1905223,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and un derstand  it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":6365,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1911591,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2938,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1914530,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":4991,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1919522,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2499,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1922022,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Female"],"rt":2160,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1924184,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What  is/are  your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English and Spanish","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Englihs ","Englihs","Englih","English and Spanish"],"rt":6983,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1931168,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["no"],"rt":2978,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1934147,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["no"],"rt":2359,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":1936509,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]